Next, we are going to add a sticker print to the costume, select the sticker tool in the 2D tool bar, select the sticker to be added in the selection window of the selected file, and press open.
On the board, click on the position of the sticker, and in the add sticker window, set the size of the sticker, and under the positioning, you can select the positioning method of the sticker, which is the distance from the outline line or the center to the outside of the board.
After setting it up, click OK, and the sticker is added.
If you want to add multiple stickers to the object window at the same time, you can select multiple stickers from the local file editor.
Drag it directly to the object window.
If you want to delete too many stickers, you can select it and click the delete button at the back.
After adding the sticker to the board, the tool automatically switches to the adjustment sticker tool.
On the sticker, there is a virtual circle.
Left-click to hold down the star circle on the circle and drag it.
You can adjust the size of the sticker, or the size of the tail.
Left-click to hold down the triangle on the circle and drag it.
You can increase or decrease the size of the sticker.
Left-click to hold down, and press the right-click at the same time.
It will pop up with a variable bought window.
Then you can set the maximum size or the exact size for the there.
After using the adjustment sticker tool to select the sticker,
you can put the provide- voir on this curve Keys.
The circle действительно appears then you can attach the sticker.
Now you can rotate the sticker.
When rotating the sticker, press right-click,
and select the possibilities under Rotation window.
Enter the specific value of the angle, click to confirm.
Left-click to press the sticker to move the sticker.
In the process of moving, right-click to enter the specific value of the moving distance in the pop-up window.
Click to confirm.
Left-click to drag the sticker of the object window to the board.
You can quickly add the sticker to the board.
Drag multiple times to add multiple stickers.
After selecting the unnecessary sticker, press the Delete key to delete it.
Select the small bear sticker on the skirt board.
Come to the object window.
Press the app key on the right side of the star sticker.
You can change the sticker here to a star sticker.
Then adjust its size and position.
In addition, after selecting the sticker with the adjustment sticker tool,
you can edit some of its properties in the property editor.
Set the surface to the grid under the sticker.
You can set the sticker to display on the front, back or front.
Repeat to copy the extension sticker along the X-axis or Y-axis.
Or spread the sticker all over the board.
At the same time, keep the original size of the sticker.
Select the star sticker.
Repeat extension along the Y-axis.
Adjust the angle of the sticker to show its value.
When the sticker is in the gap,
you can open it in the gap.
Make the sticker fully displayed.
According to the Z-axis distance,
you can adjust the vertical distance between the sticker and the board.
Connect all the colors, including the angle and positioning.
When making a flag,
if you add stickers with different positions and angles to different flags,
you have to close these two options.
The 2D position measurement can check the position of the sticker center or outer frame in the board.
Adjust the sticker tool.
When the sticker tool is in the 2D window,
right-click the sticker.
In the pop-up menu,
you can delete, copy, paste and mirror the sticker.
There are a few more options below.
I will briefly introduce their meanings.
The order can be set to the position order of the sticker.
Rotate can set the rotation angle of the sticker.
Browse the pattern.
If you use software such as AI or PS to edit and save the sticker,
you can directly update it as a new sticker.
Rotate can level or vertically rotate the sticker.
The inner pattern can be coded according to the outer outline of the sticker.
It is coded as the inner pattern.
Note that the clearer the image, the more accurate the identification.
For complex color images,
it will be coded based on the outer outline.
The custom measurement can measure the distance from the specific point of the sticker to its outline.
And create a measurement value.
The created measurement value is displayed in the property editor.
It can be renamed or deleted according to the need.
The selected sticker is easy to check the sticker.
Select the sticker in the object window.
The property editor can set its effect preset.
The option with effect preset under the material.
The default is digital print and the current presentation effect.
Click on the small triangle on the right.
You can see that there are five effects here.
The preset option can be selected.
Select a picture that uses the same material as the material.
Make the sticker use PBR pictures such as PBR pictures with the same material as the material.
The sticker change information can adjust the size of the sticker.
In this way, the sticker added to the model is completed.
Come to the property editor.
Click on the save in the upper right corner.
The sticker can be saved as .gif.
A file with the 0.gif format can be saved.
To be reused.
Click on it.
The screen has changed.
Roger the WP build.
When caper takes off.
You will see some troubles and challenges.
In order to avoid mats to slow down.
Check.
With a medium to small frame.
You can draw again.
But it can't be used.
Itez is already in the pet page by default for regardless.
Restart paper for dataд.
You can save as Cheryl's top page Letters.